http://www.agrisupply.com/privacy-policy/a/7/

Shop All
Farm Machinery & Implements Agricultural & Parts Disc & Tillage Livestock & Pets Lawn & Garden Lawn Mower Blades & Accessories Outdoor Power Equipment Truck Accessories Trailers, Tires, & Accessories Home, Shop, & Tool Hunting & Outdoor Sporting Goods Cooking, Food, & Supplies Apparel & Clothing
Featuring Top Brand Names
Top Products
Manual CanisterTool Tube Gly Star® Plus Glyphosate Cast Iron Single Burner Stove Pat's 3-Point Quick Change Hitch Wick Herbicide Applicator Keulavator™ Cultivator Frame Top 50 Products New Products Closeouts
Carolina Cooker®
Burners & Stoves Dutch Ovens Enameled Cookware Skillets. Pans, & Woks Stew, Wash, & Stock Pots BBQ Disc Blades & Discadas
Bale Movers, Spears, Feeders
Bale Spears & Bushings Movers & Forks Feeders Tarter®
Lawnmower Blades
To Fit MTD
To Fit Sears
To Fit Cub Cadet
To Fit Husqvarna
To Fit John Deere
To Fit Murray
To Fit Snapper
To Fit Toro
All Others
Estate, Flail, & Rotary Mowers
Estate, Flail, Finishing Mowers Estate Mower Parts Flail Mower Parts Rotary Mowers Rotary Mower Parts
Sprayers & Accessories
Agri Supply® Chapin® Fimco® Salvarani Solo® TIR
Pumps & Parts
Ace Pumps Delavan® Ferroni Flojet® Hypro® Pacer®
Canopies & Outdoor Furniture
Chairs, Cots, Tables Canopies & Umbrellas Pier Carts, Rod Holders Carhartt® DryWalker® Huntworth®
Toys
Featuring
Top Products Carolina Cooker® Sprayers Pumps & Parts Spears & Feeders Mower Blades Finishing & Rotary Mowers Outdoors Toys
Retail Stores
Garner, NC Greenville, NC Lumberton, NC Monroe, NC Florence, SC Petersburg, VA Statesboro, GA Tifton, GA Valdosta, GA Career Opportunities
Information
About Agri Supply Account Page Blogs Contact Us FAQ Sponsoring
Joey Gase Racing NC Seafood Festival
Account
Log In Order History Create Account
Cart (0) — $00.00
Over 26,000 Products to Choose From
Customer Service
1-800-345-0169
Submit
Privacy Policy
The Information Agri Supply Collects... and what we do with it:
Our customer's privacy and security is very important to us at Agri Supply® and subsidiary companies (collectively “ASC” or “Agri Supply”). We may periodically make needed/important changes to our policy as seen here, of which changes will be included on this page for public access. It is each customer's own responsibility to review this policy frequently and remain informed about any changes made to it, so please visit often. This posted current version of our privacy policy is effective as of February 23rd, 2015.
We only collect personal information during the process of placing an order through our web site or mail order center, mailed, phoned or faxed, or you visit one of our retail locations; when you request a copy of our catalog; when you subscribe to our email newsletter; or you initiate contact with us yourself. Our web site retains, for a variable-length period, encrypted, shopping cart activity and order information, and visitor domain. At Agri Supply, one of our top priorities is making sure that the information we have about you is protected and secure. Our web site and back end software complies with CISP guidelines. A copy of our VeriSign Certificate may be viewed from the footer of our site. We value our relationship with you and work hard to preserve your privacy and security.
We automatically recognize consumer's domain, but
we do not automatically collect email addresses. We only collect those email addresses provided to us by their owner. We collect information of those who communicate with us, or who have placed orders through us, hit counts per page, general geographical location, and browser usage of viewers, for statistical purposes to help aid us in making our website a better place for our customers.
WE COLLECT INFORMATION: When you communicate with us, the information we may collect from you is used to communicate with you. Any other information collected may be used for statistics, demographics, optimization, and/or personalization. When you make a purchase from us, the information we collect is used for the purpose of fulfilling your order, and held on file for future purchases by you, to allow for a viewable order history online of your unique purchases. When you opt-in to receive our physical and/or electronic promotional mailings, your information is used only to the extent covered in our Privacy Policy and Email Privacy Policy, and for no other reason. Should you at any time wish to stop receiving our printed catalog being mailed to your physical address, or our email newsletter and/or targeted promotional pieces coming to your email inbox, please let us know. You may opt out of either catalog or emails when you call us toll free 1-800-345-0169 or contacting us from our contact page. There is also an unsubscribe link found in every promotional email and newsletter we send out. Your privacy is our priority!
In Respect to Cookies:
We do use and set cookies on your computer to: 1) Store visitor preferences so you do not repeatedly have to reset them 2) Record session
information, such as items that you may add to your shopping cart so that you may return later to continue your order rather than have to begin again 3) Record
user-specific information on what pages you access or visit so that we understand better your interests and can show you more relevant products 4) Ensure that
you are not repeatedly sent the same promotions.
In Respect of Security Measures:
We do have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. We will share information that we have about your purchasing activities in response to subpoenas or for other verifiably legal reasons. The law permits us to share information about our current and former customers with government agencies or authorized third parties under certain legal circumstances.
Our eComm Provider's Statement: "We use 3DES encryption on both the credit card number and expiration date. When a customer enters a credit card number (through SSL encryption) the web page passes that number to a procedure that encrypts it before putting it into the database. The credit card number is decrypted only when the client downloads their orders through the admin tool. It is never decrypted into a database field.
We use SSL, SFTP or file encryption when transferring credit card data to the client's fulfillment system. The encrypted credit card data is wiped from our database after 5 days. We retain just the first digit and last 4 digits of the card# after 5 days."
Privacy & Opt Out Information:
We are committed to the responsible use of personal information for marketing purposes and our customer’s
satisfaction. We also strive to provide offers and promotions for our products and services to individuals that
are most likely to have an interest in receiving them. One way we do this is to contribute information about our customers to 3rd parties (NOTE: We do NOT buy, sell, nor rent email lists. See our Email Privacy Policy for our Newsletter Subscribers here.). In exchange, we receive additional information about our customers or new information about potential customers who may be interested in our products. By doing so, we are able to better understand our customer’s preferences and send relevant offers.
Direct Marketing Association Mail Preference and Canadian Marketing Association:
To receive less US national mail, you can register for the Direct Marketing Association's Mail Preference
Service. Most reputable direct marketers use the Mail Preference file to remove those who prefer not to
receive unsolicited offers via postal mail. You may register your name at https://www.dmachoice.org. Although you will see a great reduction in the unsolicited mail you receive, not all commercial mail will stop. You may continue to receive mail from companies with which you already do business. In addition, you may continue to receive mail from local merchants, professional and alumni associations, political candidates and office holders, and mail addressed to "resident/occupant." Please note that Mail Preference Service applies only to home addresses, not business addresses.
To receive less Canadian national mail, you can register through the Canadian Marketing Association’s Do
Not Contact Service. You may register your name at https://www.the-cma.org/?WCE=C=47|K=224217.
Customers & Prospects:
As a customer of ours, we value and respect your privacy and will gladly remove you from just our customer list. In doing so, please understand that you will not receive promotions such as our catalog. If you would like to continue to receive our catalog, but prefer that we not share your name with third parties for marketing purposes, we will gladly remove you from our share list and place your name on our Do Not Share List. Please visit our contact page with your request.
×
Close
× Sign Up For Email Newsletters
Close
